Lands' End All-American Quilt Collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
Guides to the Collections in the Archive of the American Folklife Center
Lands' End All-American Quilt Collection 1992-1997
AFC 1997/011
Archive of Folk Culture, American Folklife Center, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
61.5 linear feet (154 boxes)
Total approximately 80,543 items.
Lands' End, Inc.
The collection consists of photographs of quilts and quilters, essays, entry forms, and a few fabric and needlework samples submitted in three nationwide contests in 1992, 1994, and 1996 sponsored by Coming Home, a division of Lands’ End, Inc. home shopping service, and Good Housekeeping magazine. Approximately 13,100 entries for the three contests came from all 50 states and the District of Columbia with a few from Canada. Many styles of needlework, quilting, patchwork, appliqué, and embroidery are represented in the visual materials. The collection also includes correspondence and surveys from some contestants and administrative files related to judging the entries, exhibitions, and publicity.
Scope and Content
The Lands' End All-American Quilt Collection consists of visual images, essays, entry forms, and administrative materials from three quilt contests held in 1992, 1994, and 1996. The collection was donated to the American Folklife Center by Lands' End in 1997. The 1996 national first place winning quilt, made by Candy Goff of Montana, was displayed at the reception to celebrate the 20th anniversary of the establishment of the American Folklife Center at the Library of Congress in September 1996.
The contests were sponsored jointly by Coming Home, the linens and home-decorating division of Lands' End, Inc., a catalog and home-shopping service, and Good Housekeeping magazine. Those entering the contest were asked to submit a color photo or slide of the quilt. "If Quilts Could Talk" was the theme for 1994 and 1996, and a 100-word essay on the theme was required of finalists in 1994 and for entries in 1996.
The rules for the contest specified that quilts must be of an original design or an original interpretation of a traditional pattern, and no quilts made from kits would be considered. Quilts made by groups and children were also eligible. Monetary prizes of $10,000, $3,000, and $2,000 were awarded to the national first, second, and third place winners. Additionally, a winner was named from each state and the District of Columbia, and those winners were awarded $100 gift certificates from Coming Home. Winners were announced and photographs of their quilts were published in the Good Housekeeping magazine and the Coming Home catalog.
Each year a panel of five distinguished judges made their choices based on quality of workmanship, quilting techniques, suitability of fabrics, color choices, over-all design, eye appeal, and originality. From among thousands of entries submitted, 250 finalist quilts were selected each year to be shipped to Lands' End headquarters in Dodgeville, Wisconsin, where the judges made final selections (See Appendix: Names of Finalists) in choosing the year's winners.
The winning entries are arranged initially by prize and then alphabetically within the following categories-- National, Judges' Choice, Kids' Quilts, and State winners. Each folder contains the contestants' original entries (including slides, photos, personal essays, and forms) and a survey of contestant information requested by the American Folklife Center for the online presentation, “Quilts and Quiltmaking in America, 1978-1996.”
Other items in the collection include photographs from the judging activities of 1996 (folders 36-46), and the entries to an employee quilt contest at Lands' End staged in 1992 (folders 3114-3131).
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Akana, Elizabeth A.; Allison, Mary Ann K.; Alltizer, Leona.; Anderson, Jennifer Jared.; Arakaki, Nancy.; Aruns, Jane.; Averett, Linda.; Baggett, Gladys.; Ballard, Debra.; Balunis, Evelyn F.; Baugh, Catherine.; Bawn, Rosemary.; Beecroft, Anne Tisdel.; Benzo, Terry.; Berry, Irene G.; Bolton, Pat.; Brooks, Kathleen Rindal, 1956-; Bryan, Mamie.; Bryant, Jill D.; Burge, Shelly.; Burrill, Jean F.; Butler, Barbara, 1944-; Calhoun, Frances B.; Calistro, Polly.; Cameron, Charlotte.; Chase, Lori.; Choate, Donna.; Clabo, Margo J., 1947-; Clarine, Barbara.; Clarke, Eileen, 1948-; Denaxas, Pat.; Denenberg, Rita.; Dick, Betty E.; Dison, Deanna D.; Dubbs, Kathleen.; Dunn, Frances V.; Elmer, Susan E.; Elvgren, B. J.; Encarnación, Patricia.; Erlenborn, Dorothy C.; Evans, Jane R., 1954-; Fahl, Ann, 1947-; Finlayson, Constance.; Fisher, Emma M.; Fraley, Ted.; Fuquay, Susan.; Fusco, Mary Bartlett.; Gant, Alice.; Gaudynski, Diane.; Gillihan, Anne.; Glaze, Sally.; Goff, Candy.; Gould, Patricia.; Greenhoe-Bergh, Eliza.; Gresham, Mabel.; Haglund, Joan R.; Hague, Elizabeth A.; Haider, Vicky.; Hall, Jane, 1932-; Harbison, Edna R.; Harshbarger, Linda.; Hattaway, Cesarina.; Haywood, Dixie.; Hearst, Lavena.; Hedin, Susan R.; Hegge, Ken.; Hire, Dianne S.; Holihan, Jane.; Hughes, Margaret (Quiltmaker); Ingersoll, Patricia, 1937-; Inverso, Therese M.; Jordan, Ethel Taylor.; Kailhofer, Patricia.; Keehr, Brenda.; Kepaa, Rita.; Kimball, Annabelle.; Kimball, Charlene.; Kinnear, Geri.; Klipfel, Leah.; Koehler, Fran.; Krauss, Joanne L.; Kruelskie, Patricia.; Laceky, Carolyn.; Landkamer, Ginny.; Lee, Kathy A.; Ludwig, Janet, 1945-; Lutz, Marcia.; Manzanares, Helen.; Matthews, Pat J.; McAlister, Mary Alma.; McCabe, Mary Jo, 1936-; McCoy, Susanne.; McKie, Barbara Barrick.; McLennand, Sara Ann.; McNutt-Kaestner, Cindy.; McWilliams, Margaret C.; Medovic, Cathy.; Metz, Pearl.; Miller, Dianne (Quiltmaker); Millward, Hazel I.; Morris, Ruth W.; Musick, Ruann.; Myers, Dorothy A.; Nancarrow, Ree.; Newman, Terrie.; Nicholson, Naomi.; Null, Nancy Marzilli.; Olson, Noelle M.; Ott, Carol K.; Parks, Laura Bailey.; Patch, Adele.; Patton, Ila, 1905-2001.; Paul, Anna Mae.; Pelletier, Sophie.; Perea, Ilse.; Potter, Maggie.; Prentice, Royce H.; Ramsey, Kathy.; Rasso, Nancy.; Reisch, Lori.; Richards, Rhonda (Rhonda L.), 1968-; Rouse, Kathryn.; Schell, Ann-Lillian.; Schutt, Suzanne Peery.; Schwam, Vicki.; Scoggan, Pam.; Seay, J. Alex.; Seigel, Rebekka.; Sells, Audree L.; Sewell, Natalie.; Sewell, Sonja.; Shaw, Leslie B.; Shockley, Maggie.; Sierra, Lois.; Simmons, Lorraine E.; Singer, Vivian R.; Smith, Karen A. (Quiltmaker); Smith, Sandra E., 1942-; Spencer, Jeannette E.; Splitt, Martha.; Stanley, Lura, 1906-1984.; Stewart, Joyce, 1939-; Strasberg, Lois.; Styring, Patricia.; Sugiyama, Yuki.; Thompson, Judith I.; Timby, Deborah Bird.; Todd, Zenna, 1916-2012.; Tucker, Daren L.; Tummings, LaQuita.; Webb, Marianne P.; Weber, Julia C.; White, Norma.; Witteman, Lori.; Wood, Sherri.; Woodfield, Marlene Brown.; Wortman, Penelope.; Ziegler, Madge.; Zocher, Judie.
Organizations
American Folklife Center.; Archive of Folk Culture (Library of Congress); Lands' End All-American Quilt Contest.; Lands' End, Inc.; Library of Congress. National Digital Library Program.
Subjects
Album quilts--United States.; Appliqué--United States.; Children's quilts--United States.; Contests--United States.; Crazy quilts--United States.; Crib quilts--United States.; Double wedding ring quilts--United States.; Embroidery--United States.; Friendship quilts--United States.; Log cabin quilts--United States.; Machine appliqué--United States.; Needlework--United States.; Patchwork quilts--United States.; Quilting--Competitions--United States.; Quiltmakers--United States.; Quilts--Canada.; Quilts--United States.; Star quilts--United States.; Strip quilting--United States.; Trapunto--United States.
Titles
Good housekeeping.; Quilts and quiltmaking in America, 1978-1996.
Form/Genre
Correspondence.; Essays.; Manuscripts.; Needlework.; Negatives.; Photographic prints.; Quilting.; Slides.
Provenance
In 1992, 1994, and 1996, Coming Home (the Bed & Bath Division of Lands' End Inc.) co-sponsored a national quilting contest with Good Housekeeping magazine. Taking into account the dissemination of promotional material, the processing of entries, and the selection of winners, each contest took approximately two years to complete. Due to the nature and scope of the contest, in 1994, the Archive of the American Folklife Center expressed interest in co-sponsorship; however, after some deliberation, the Archive instead chose to recommend candidates for the 1996 judging panel. After Lands' End announced its decision to discontinue the contest, the Archive expressed interest in acquiring the winning contest materials for their collections.
In September 1996, the acquisition of the Lands' End gift was officially announced at the 20th anniversary celebration/board meeting of American Folklife Center when the 1996 first place national winner made by Candy Goff of Montana was displayed at the meeting reception. The Archive received collection materials between late fall of 1996 and early 1997. In the spring of 1997, the collection was chosen by Librarian of Congress Dr. James Billington for digitization for the American Memory online presentation on the Library of Congress website. The resulting web presentation “Quilts and Quiltmaking in America, 1978-1996” was released in the summer of 1999.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in the following series: Series I. Administrative files for 1992, 1994, and 1996 (Boxes 1 to 6); Series II. Contest entries, for 1992 (Boxes 7 to 55), 1994 (Boxes 56 to 108), and 1996 (Boxes 109 to 147) and an oversized box (Box 148); and Series III Contest winners 1992, 1994, 1996 (Boxes 149 to 154). Posters featuring the 1996 winners are housed in the map cabinet drawer.
Within each of the three years of the contest, the entries are organized alphabetically by states. Within each state, entries are organized alphabetically by last names of the contestants. Washington, D.C. appears as "District of Columbia." Each folder may contain both manuscript and visual materials. Thus a typical folder of entry consists of the original envelope submitted by the contestant; the contest entry forms; essays and newspaper articles (if submitted), photographs and/or slides and negatives, and in some cases, samples of fabrics used in the quilts.
Winning entries were not processed as part of the original collection because they were separated out for digital conversion (See Boxes 149-154) in 1999. As a result, they were processed in August 2002 by Rosemary Graham and Valda Morris-Slack and form Series III.
Access
The collection is open for research. Access restrictions apply, some collection materials are stored offsite; please contact the Folklife Reading Room before requesting materials at 202-707-5510, folklife@loc.gov.
Online Content
National and state winning entries from the three contests are available in the presentation “Quilts and Quiltmaking in America, 1978-1996.” See http://hdl.loc.gov/loc.afc/collafc.af000010, an online resource compiled by the National Digital Library Program of the Library of Congress.
Related Materials
A Stitch in Time: African American Quilters of Oakland, AFC 1991/010
Alliance for American Quilts Interview Collection, AFC 2007/009
Blue Ridge Parkway Folklife Project Collection, AFC 1982/009
Lisa Oshins Quilt Survey Collection, AFC 1988/033
Quilts and Quiltmaking in America, 1978-1996 Online Presentation Collection, AFC 1999/024
The Quilters' Save Our Stories Project, Lecture by Bernard L. Herman, AFC 2007/034
Collection Inventory and Description
- Series I: Administrative Materials (Box 1-6)
  - 1992 (Box 1)
    - Collection Guide including attachments. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Sample of folder contents (Box 1, Folder 1B)
      Contains materials which were requested for the competition.
    - Preliminary materials - Part A (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Preliminary materials - Part B (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Smithsonian controversy on Chinese made quilts. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Administrative materials and correspondence (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Budget and expenses: Judges' shipping (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Contest Rules (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Judges (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Judging - "Guidelines for Evaluation” (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Houston Quilt Show. Brochures, programs and flyers of the International Quilt Festival held in at the George R. Brown Convention Center, Texas. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Winners - List and working papers (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Winners - Receipts for gift certificates (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Exhibit - Lands' End (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Press Release concerning Smithsonian pattern made by West Virginia Quilters (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Complete computer printout of entries (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 1994 (Box 2)
    - Administrative materials and correspondence (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Contest coordinator's (Michelle Casper) working documents (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Announcement of Contest (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Budget, expenses, and shipping documents (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Entry forms (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Sample letters to entrants (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Judges' “Guidelines for Evaluation,” Evaluation sheets (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Screening process and “Quilt Key” (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Houston Quilt Show (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Press releases (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Promotional materials (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Coming Home (Lands' End Catalog) and Fact Sheets (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Computer printout of entrants, Complete (8 1⁄2 x 14" - see oversize box) (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - 1996 (Box 3)
    - Administrative materials and correspondence (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Work plan. Contains the work plan for the 1996 Quilt Contest. (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Announcements of contest (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Expenses (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Travel of Judges (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Judges and Candidates (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Judges: Christine Thurman, correspondence (Box 3, Folder 34A)
    - Judges' “Guidelines for Evaluation” (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Photographs of judging activities and winners' reception (Continued at folder 42) (Box 3, Folder 36-41)
    - Photographs of judging activities and winners' reception (Continued from folder 41) (Box 4, Folder 42-46)
    - Quilt shows outside Lands' End (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Quilt Show at Lands' End (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Reception for Quilt Show at Lands' End (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Winners' essays for display (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Winners, information about (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Promotional materials for the contest (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - “Our Home” Essays (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Publicity (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Publicity kits (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Newspaper articles about crafts (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Publications on Quilts and Quilting - Part 1 of 2 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Publications on Quilts and Quilting - Part 2 of 2 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Library of Congress-Acquisition and reception, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Computer printouts of entries from Lands' End, Incomplete (Box 6, Folder 60)
- Series II: Contest Entries, Every item is accessible by the year of entry, the state, folder number, and personal name. Please consult with the reference staff at the Folklife Reading Room. (Box 7-148)
  - 1992 Entries (Box 7-55)
    - Alabama (Box 7, Folder 61-102)
    - Alaska (Box 7, Folder 103-120)
    - Arizona (Box 8, Folder 121-156)
    - Arkansas (Box 8, Folder 157-187)
    - California (Box 9, Folder 188-252)
    - California (Box 10, Folder 253-317)
    - California (Box 11, Folder 318-340)
    - California (Box 12, Folder 341-399)
    - Colorado (Box 13, Folder 400-469)
    - Connecticut (Box 14, Folder 470-532)
    - Delaware (Box 14, Folder 533-541)
    - District of Columbia (Box 14, Folder 542-544)
    - Florida (Box 15, Folder 545-613)
    - Florida (Box 16, Folder 614-695)
    - Georgia (Box 17, Folder 696-760)
    - Hawaii (Box 17, Folder 761-769)
    - Idaho (Box 18, Folder 770-781)
    - Illinois (Box 18, Folder 782-827)
    - Illinois (Box 19, Folder 828-876)
    - Illinois (Box 20, Folder 877-919)
    - Indiana (Box 20, Folder 920-943)
    - Indiana (Box 21, Folder 944-991)
    - Iowa (Box 21, Folder 992-1005)
    - Iowa (Box 22, Folder 1006-1021)
    - Kansas (Box 22, Folder 1022-1063)
    - Kentucky (Box 23, Folder 1064-1109)
    - Louisiana (Box 23, Folder 1110-1127)
    - Maine (Box 24, Folder 1128-1173)
    - Maryland (Box 25, Folder 1174-1207)
    - Massachusetts (Box 25, Folder 1208-1237)
    - Massachusetts (Box 26, Folder 1238-1303)
    - Michigan (Box 27, Folder 1304-1381)
    - Michigan (Box 28, Folder 1382-1433)
    - Minnesota (Box 29, Folder 1434-1516)
    - Mississippi (Box 30, Folder 1517-1543)
    - Missouri (Box 30, Folder 1544-1580)
    - Missouri (Box 31, Folder 1581-1619)
    - Montana (Box 31, Folder 1620-1645)
    - Nebraska (Box 32, Folder 1646-1675)
    - Nevada (Box 32, Folder 1676-1686)
    - New Hampshire (Box 32, Folder 1687-1707)
    - New Jersey (Box 33, Folder 1708-1766)
    - New Jersey (Box 34, Folder 1767-1813)
    - New Mexico (Box 34, Folder 1814-1826)
    - New York (Box 35, Folder 1827-1885)
    - New York (Box 36, Folder 1886-1938)
    - New York (Box 37, Folder 1939-2004)
    - North Carolina (Box 38, Folder 2005-2061)
    - North Carolina (Box 39, Folder 2062-2086)
    - North Dakota (Box 39, Folder 2087-2103)
    - Ohio (Box 40, Folder 2104-2168)
    - Ohio (Box 41, Folder 2169-2249)
    - Oklahoma (Box 42, Folder 2250-2279)
    - Oregon (Box 42, Folder 2280-2330)
    - Pennsylvania (Box 43, Folder 2331-2407)
    - Pennsylvania (Box 44, Folder 2408-2490)
    - Pennsylvania (Box 45, Folder 2491-2521)
    - Rhode Island (Box 45, Folder 2522-2530)
    - South Carolina (Box 45, Folder 2531-2564)
    - South Dakota (Box 46, Folder 2565-2581)
    - Tennessee (Box 46, Folder 2582-2627)
    - Texas (Box 46, Folder 2628-2634)
    - Texas (Box 47, Folder 2635-2704)
    - Texas (Box 48, Folder 2705-2777)
    - Utah (Box 49, Folder 2778-2805)
    - Vermont (Box 49, Folder 2806-2825)
    - Virginia (Box 50, Folder 2826-2877)
    - Virginia (Box 51, Folder 2878-2892)
    - Washington (Box 51, Folder 2893-2913)
    - Washington (Box 52, Folder 2914-2966)
    - West Virginia (Box 53, Folder 2967-2986)
    - Wisconsin (Box 53, Folder 2987-3016)
    - Wisconsin (Box 54, Folder 3017-3074)
    - Wisconsin (Box 55, Folder 3075-3107)
    - Wyoming (Box 55, Folder 3108-3113)
    - Employee Contest (held in 1992) (Box 55, Folder 3114-3131)
  - 1994 Entries (Box 56-108)
    - Alabama (Box 56, Folder 3132-3176)
    - Alaska (Box 56, Folder 3177-3188)
    - Arizona (Box 57, Folder 3189-3254)
    - Arkansas (Box 58, Folder 3255-3330)
    - Arkansas (Box 59, Folder 3331-3392)
    - California (Box 59, Folder 3393-3400)
    - California (Box 60, Folder 3401-3469)
    - California (Box 61, Folder 3470-3534)
    - California (Box 62, Folder 3535-3594)
    - California (Box 63, Folder 3595-3625)
    - Colorado (Box 63, Folder 3626-3664)
    - Colorado (Box 64, Folder 3665-3691)
    - Connecticut (Box 64, Folder 3692-3732)
    - Delaware (Box 65, Folder 3733-3749)
    - District of Columbia (Box 65, Folder 3750-3756)
    - Florida (Box 65, Folder 3757-3798)
    - Florida (Box 66, Folder 3799-3870)
    - Florida (Box 67, Folder 3871-3937)
    - Florida (Box 68, Folder 3938-3963)
    - Georgia (Box 68, Folder 3964-4004)
    - Georgia (Box 69, Folder 4005-4036)
    - Hawaii (Box 69, Folder 4037-4048)
    - Idaho (Box 69, Folder 4049-4073)
    - Illinois (Box 70, Folder 4074-4146)
    - Illinois (Box 71, Folder 4147-4223)
    - Illinois (Box 72, Folder 4224-4231)
    - Indiana (Box 72, Folder 4232-4290)
    - Iowa (Box 73, Folder 4291-4362)
    - Kansas (Box 74, Folder 4363-4414)
    - Kentucky (Box 75, Folder 4415-4447)
    - Louisiana (Box 76, Folder 4448-4476)
    - Maine (Box 76, Folder 4477-4509)
    - Maryland (Box 76, Folder 4510-4522)
    - Maryland (Box 77, Folder 4523-4585)
    - Massachusetts (Box 78, Folder 4586-4656)
    - Massachusetts (Box 79, Folder 4657-4671)
    - Michigan (Box 79, Folder 4672-4737)
    - Michigan (Box 80, Folder 4738-4800)
    - Minnesota (Box 80, Folder 4801-4823)
    - Minnesota (Box 81, Folder 4824-4887)
    - Mississippi (Box 81, Folder 4888-4912)
    - Missouri (Box 82, Folder 4913-5005)
    - Montana (Box 83, Folder 5006-5033)
    - Nebraska (Box 83, Folder 5034-5073)
    - Nevada (Box 83, Folder 5074-5087)
    - New Hampshire (Box 84, Folder 5088-5114)
    - New Jersey (Box 84, Folder 5115-5149)
    - New Jersey (Box 85, Folder 5150-5194)
    - New Mexico (Box 86, Folder 5195-5222)
    - New York (Box 86, Folder 5223-5275)
    - New York (Box 87, Folder 5276-5357)
    - New York (Box 88, Folder 5358-5404)
    - North Carolina (Box 88, Folder 5405-5434)
    - North Carolina (Box 89, Folder 5435-4391)
    - North Dakota (Box 90, Folder 4392-5512)
    - Ohio (Box 90, Folder 5513-5561)
    - Ohio (Box 91, Folder 5562-5632)
    - Ohio (Box 92, Folder 5633-5712)
    - Oklahoma (Box 93, Folder 5713-5771)
    - Oregon (Box 94, Folder 5772-5846)
    - Pennsylvania (Box 95, Folder 5847-5915)
    - Pennsylvania (Box 96, Folder 5916-5977)
    - Pennsylvania (Box 97, Folder 5978-6024)
    - Rhode Island (Box 98, Folder 6025-6037)
    - South Carolina (Box 98, Folder 6038-6067)
    - South Dakota (Box 98, Folder 6068-6086)
    - Tennessee (Box 99, Folder 6087-6154)
    - Tennessee (Box 100, Folder 6155-6170)
    - Texas (Box 100, Folder 6171-6221)
    - Texas (Box 101, Folder 6222-6301)
    - Texas (Box 102, Folder 6302-6319)
    - Utah (Box 102, Folder 6320-6343)
    - Vermont (Box 102, Folder 6344-6361)
    - Virginia (Box 103, Folder 6362-6424)
    - Virginia (Box 104, Folder 6425-6465)
    - Washington (Box 104, Folder 6466-6492)
    - Washington (Box 105, Folder 6492-6552)
    - West Virginia (Box 106, Folder 6553-6625)
    - West Virginia (Box 107, Folder 6626-6690)
    - Wisconsin (Box 108, Folder 6691-6710)
    - Wyoming (Box 108, Folder 6711-6733)
    - Canada (Box 108, Folder 6734)
    - APO: U.S. Mission to NATO (Box 108, Folder 6735)
  - 1996 Entries (Box 109-148)
    - Alabama (Box 109, Folder 6736-6763)
    - Alaska (Box 109, Folder 6764-6776)
    - Arizona (Box 109, Folder 6777-6788)
    - Arizona (Box 110, Folder 6789-6819)
    - Arkansas (Box 110, Folder 6820-6836)
    - California (Box 111, Folder 6837-6894)
    - California (Box 112, Folder 6895-6951)
    - California (Box 113, Folder 6952-6994)
    - Colorado (Box 114, Folder 6995-7049)
    - Connecticut (Box 115, Folder 7050-7072)
    - Delaware (Box 115, Folder 7073-7075)
    - District of Columbia (Box 115, Folder 7076)
    - Florida (Box 115, Folder 7077-7114)
    - Florida (Box 116, Folder 7115-7173)
    - Georgia (Box 117, Folder 7174-7226)
    - Hawaii (Box 118, Folder 7227-7238)
    - Idaho (Box 118, Folder 7239-7261)
    - Illinois (Box 118, Folder 7262-7289)
    - Illinois (Box 119, Folder 7290-7341)
    - Illinois (Box 120, Folder 7342-7353)
    - Indiana (Box 120, Folder 7354-7403)
    - Iowa (Box 121, Folder 7404-7446)
    - Kansas (Box 121, Folder 7447-7477)
    - Kentucky (Box 122, Folder 7478-7522)
    - Louisiana (Box 122, Folder 7523-7539)
    - Louisiana (Box 123, Folder 7540-7553)
    - Maine (Box 123, Folder 7554-7561)
    - Maryland (Box 123, Folder 7562-7592)
    - Massachusetts (Box 124, Folder 7593-7638)
    - Michigan (Box 125, Folder 7639-7686)
    - Michigan (Box 126, Folder 7687-7739)
    - Minnesota (Box 127, Folder 7740-7803)
    - Mississippi (Box 128, Folder 7804-7813)
    - Missouri (Box 128, Folder 7814-7859)
    - Missouri (Box 129, Folder 7860-7867)
    - Montana (Box 129, Folder 7868-7884)
    - Nebraska (Box 129, Folder 7885-7907)
    - Nevada (Box 129, Folder 7908-7913)